const STORE = [
  {
      question: "Thereâ€™s ways to survive these times, and I think one way is the shape the telling takes.",
      answers: [
        'Toni Morrison', // 0
        'Ali Smith', // 1
        'George Saunders', // 2
        'J.K. Rowling', // 3
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Ali Smith'
    },

    {
      question: "If they can get you asking the wrong questions, they don't have to worry about answers.",
      answers: [
        'James Baldwin',
        'Thomas Pynchon',
        'Hanya Yanagihara',
        'David Mitchell',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Thomas Pynchon',
    },

    {
      question: "That which exists without my knowledge exists without my permission.",
      answers: [
        'Richard Ford',
        'Cormac McCarthy',
        'Jodi Picoult',
        'Kurt Vonnegut',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Cormac McCarthy',
    },

    {
      question: 'I think the deepest level of our freedom is being able to change our identity.',
      answers: [
        'Roxanne Gay',
        'Olga Tokarczuk',
        'Colson Whitehead',
        'Tom Robbins',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Olga Tokarczuk',
    },

    {
      question: 'Sometimes human beings have to just sit in one place and, like, hurt.',
      answers: [
        'Andrew Stevens',
        'Chase Burke',
        'Kyle Macy',
        'David Foster Wallace',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'David Foster Wallace',
    },

    {
      question: 'Prohibition is the trigger of crime.',
      answers: [
        'Tom Clancy',
        'John Grisham',
        'Dashiell Hammett',
        'Ian Fleming',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Ian Fleming',
    },

    {
      question: 'Every moment happens twice: inside and outside, and they are two different histories.',
      answers: [
        'Zadie Smith',
        'Maragret Atwood',
        'Sarah Vowell',
        'ZZ Packer',
      ],
      correctAnswer:'Zadie Smith',
    },

    {
      question: 'Life is to be lived, not controlled; and humanity is won by continuing to play in face of certain defeat.',
      answers: [
        'Elena Ferrante',
        'Ralph Ellison',
        'Jonathan Letham',
        'Amy Hempel',
      ],
      correctAnswer:'Ralph Ellison',
    },

    {
      question: "Everything passes. Nobody gets anything for keeps. And that's how we've got to live.",
      answers: [
        'Yaa Gyasi',
        'Vladamir Nabokov',
        'Haruki Murakami',
        'Lorrie Moore',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Haruki Murakami',
    },

    {
      question: 'History is a nightmare from which I am trying to awake.',
      answers: [
        'Ernest Hemingway',
        'Virginia Woolf',
        'John Dos Passos',
        'James Joyce',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'James Joyce',
    }
];
